searchengine.us 2017-06-27

# None

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is extremely important to us. Following is our policy regarding how we protect the privacy of the personal information you provide us. XODO Inc collects information when you register with XODO Inc. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code, your address and others. XODO Inc automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, XODO Inc cookie information and another accessible information.

XODO Inc uses information for the following general purposes: improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

XODO Inc does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances: -We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with XODO Inc under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your information to help XODO Inc communicate with you about offers from XODO Inc and our marketing partners. -We respond to court orders or legal process.

XODO Inc does not provide any individually identifiable information to the advertiser.

Cookies 

XODO Inc may set and access XODO Inc cookies on your computer. XODO Inc lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages and/or network to set and access their cookies on your computer.

Surveys 

From time to time, we or a company selected by us may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys. You may be asked to provide membership information to participate. All surveys are optional.

Contests 

We may from time to time offer you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, product giveaways and similar services. You will be asked to provide membership information to participate in any sweepstakes or giveaways. We or a company selected by us administers the sweepstakes and contacts the winner. All sweepstakes are optional.

Advertising 

We use our own advertising as well as third party advertising agencies. We cannot be held responsible for anything contained within our partners, our members, or our advertisers sites.

Permission To Use Your Content 

By transmitting any suggestions, information, identification, material, or other content ("content") to us, you automatically grant us the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, redistribute, transmit, perform and display such content (in whole or part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in such content. Further, we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, and suggestions contained in any communications you send to this Site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to creating, manufacturing, and marketing products and/or services using such information.

General 

Communications from XODO Inc, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the XODO Inc Newsletter, are considered part of XODO Inc membership and you may not opt out of receiving them. We limit access to information about you to employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your XODO Inc Account Information is password-protected.

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

XODO Inc may update Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to you. Please check these Privacy Policy periodically for changes. By using XODO Inc web site after changes have been made to Privacy Policy, you agree to the changes.
